### Profile

I'm a 8-year experienced Frontend web developer with React.js, Angular, Vue, Next.js.

I'm always updates my knowledge about the latest changes and the latest technology.

I understands the concrete knowledge and the new advanced topics of React and other modern javascript frameworks. I will always make sure the project is caught up with the up-to-date

I'm strong with Styled-component or any CSS pre-processing such as SASS, or LESS, and will be able to build and style the React components from the design.

I have a good eye and care a lot about user experience, I can develop any nice looking animations or UI effect that will appeal to the user.

I understand all the concrete knowledge of SEO and I am able to develop an optimized web app or optimize existing web apps to make them search engine friendly.

### Professional Experience

### Full stack developer, Octopus energy

09/2020 - 09/2022

Working on staking, bond, farming, calculator

- Developed Gyro Calculator based on react/Web3, GraphQL, **Smart Contract.**
- Designed Gyro Dapp for mobile and desktop, building website using React/TS.
- · Community on Gyro Dao for funding and boosting

### Senior Front end Developer, CMI SAFE COMPANY ☑

07/2018 - 05/2020 | Carlton, Australia

- Analyzed original Angular codes and then developed a new Website using React + Next.js + Blitz.js, reducing site response time by 2x.
- Implemented complex UI components with React/TypeScript and CSS.
- In collaboration with the sales team and data scientists, developed lead & feedback analysis system with Python Django+React and Elasticsearch, increasing sales rate by 20%.

### Senior Full stack developer, X-TEAM □

04/2016 - 05/2018 | Australia

• Worked on providing API endpoints with Node.js/Inversify and MongoDB.

Built from scratch admin platform for managing platform's database entities and users using React,

- Node.js, and Mongoose.
- Developed 50+ Node.js APIs and integrated with Salesforce CRM, providing real time data to managers.
- Improved the UX by creating several components.
- Wrote scripts to use and manipulate data from various sources

# Katashi Fujino

## Full stack developer

- **+**1 443 422 3753
- Westminster, Maryland , USA
- His/He
- kryptify
- FairPlay#9808
- website
- in Katashi-fujino

### Skills

React	• • • • •
Next.js	• • • • •
Angular	• • • • •
Typescript	• • • • •
Nest.js	• • • •
Django	• • • •
Node.js	• • • • •
AWS	• • • •
MySQL	• • • • •
Javascript	• • • • •
PostgreSQL	• • • • •
Django	• • • • •
Express.js	• • • • •
MongoDB	• • • •

### Education

### **Bachelor of Computer Science,**

University of Toronto □ 04/2012 - 04/2014

Learned Algorithm design, programming languages, database systems, artificial intelligence, and pattern information processing systems.

## **S** Languages

• English

## **♂** Interests

- Swimming
- Traveling
- Soccer